Bye, baby girl.
>> Bye. And I know I will pick you up from
Claremont from school on Thursday.
>> Okay, then we'll go around and shop.
Bye, little girl. Love you.
>> I'm not going now. I'm supposed to bring
Allison to school, but no. No.
>> Bye.
>> Bye. I'll see you Thursday, baby.
>> I'm I'm leaving.
>> Wow. No, I I asked Alison to leave it
with mom. Alvaro got tona.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. Thanks. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> Bye baby. Bye
for
that. Bye
guys. Relax and chill.
One hour drive going and one hour drive
coming back home. So lot lot of coffee.
I have chocolate. I have coffee. Oh my
goodness. Okay. Can I have my Hawaiian
bread? Hawaiian bread.
Second day.
[Music]
Show off.
Collab with Prada. Okay. Channel collab
with Prada. Okay. Tik Tok.
Okay.
I have chocolate. I have coffee. Guys,
decide what I like. Okay, let's go nang
to Beverly Hills Center later. Beverly
Hills Center. Okay. Okay. I'll dress up
now after this
coffee. Okay. Shower a finish outfit.
Okay. Disclaimer. The sole purpose of
this video is purely for entertainment.
Of course, no bashing. It's for fun. Of
course,
[Music]
So, okay. Today we'll have dinner with
friends and of course I'm so excited
with the food. And where's Phil? Phil,
let's go. So, I'll see my my dear
friends Nikki and Christa. So, I was not
able to see them last trip. So, I'll
meet with them today.
Okay. Let's go. See you, Tad. Bye, TJ.
Okay.
>> Wow. What a nice outdo
lot. Okay. Don't forget to ano to
marinate the point.
Okay. Marinate ano. You boil it par.
>> And then later when they get okay.
>> Okay. Poat po sir.
Okay. my dinner
and I'm stay alone here.
I go somewhere.
I cook and pork chop. So, we're now in
town and of course, this is so amazing
here. Beautiful and nice, as I always
say. And look how beautiful the interior
is. It's so um an what adjective?
>> The intricate details.
>> Look at the intricate details.
It's so spectacular here. And look how
beautiful. So tonight we'll have dinner
here and celebrate Phil's birthday. So
let's go.
>> Christa, it's so dark.
>> I can't see. Wow, it's so beautiful
here, guys. Sorry for being late.
Sorry.
>> Christa said happy birthday.
>> Happy birthday.
>> Christa's greeting you. Did you say
thanks?
>> Thank you.
>> Okay.
>> Just for trial.
>> Yeah. Then weren't going back.
>> No, you know about it. Kevin, you know
about it.
>> Perfect. Remember guys, just a reminder,
everything is meant to be shared here.
Um, all of our protein plants, all of
our chicken, beef, and fish all the car.
We do have rice, noodles to pair with it
on the next page.
>> So, okay. This is my sushi.
[Music]
Thank you.
>> Bye. Thank you. Thank you.
>> So, let's call it a night. Good night,
guys. It's so dark here. So, where are
we? And stop.
>> And we enjoyed and thank you so much for
dinner
>> always.
>> Next is dimum.
>> Okay. Night girl.
>> Night.
>> So, wow. This is so nice. Look at this.
The bedroom.
>> Okay. I like this. But if you like it,
I'll get for you. Is this nice already?
So, okay. I'll get this. Your sister
didn't like it.
>> My sister she wants it for me.
>> So it's good.
The one in the man is like really like
no sir
shopping
guys
$20 sir.
Thank you po
wear this these shoes. I'm just trying
this. We don't remember the alteration
but they said it's nice. Where can I
wear this?
42. Yes or no? Too old for this. Okay.
You're glowing in it. You really are.
Mom, Tiffany Blue sunglasses. Mom,
Tiffany blue. Tiffany blue. PJ, is this
nice on me? Is this Tony blue? No. I
like Okay, I'll get it.
isn't they don't
>> Yeah,
>> so there's there's one there's only six
in the in the in the US.
>> Six in the US,
>> but they're not crazy.
They're actually
>> They're 3.90.
>> How much is 300? Not bad. Just get it.
Thank you.
Mom
watch
Rolex. Rolex po.
That's Bolex, guys. Matching t. Oh my
god.
Wow.
Bolex.
Can you look at the Bolex? I have that
one, too. Lot jet lag blood. She's a
luxury.
>> Oh, yeah. Okay, guys. Anto Glorio Drive.
Ma'oam,
[Music]
guys.
pray walking walking walking nil si mom
s Alexander
guys PJ of course we're now in Rodeo
Rodeo of course I forget just correct me
so we're now here at the John store okay
and of course look how beautiful custom
made and of course with the famous
yellow car of the John
store picture.
How beautiful was this one?
Very beautiful. Look at the exterior. It
used to be there across Hermes beside
Hermes. They moved here and you know
they made it exactly the same um
exterior. Look how beautiful. Exactly
the same. Imagine. And with a famous
yellow car.
>> Oh my god. Look at this. They have for
the house of Gujan like so beautiful
like custom made for like presidents
of the country.
It's okay.
Sexy mother
picture.
Okay. Posing. Posing. Okay. Pose. Post.
Pose. Ganya lang. Okay. Pose. Pose.
Pose. Pose. Pose. Si mom. Sir Joseph. I
sar
[Music]
Carolina. Don't you have the one with
the long sleeve sequence?
>> Did you feel long sleeve?
>> What about the sequence?
>> This is so bad. again. Let me hold up.
Blackh.
Oh my god.
Mama J. This one.
>> This. What brand is that?
>> This one. It is actually a rubble.
My god. This is the other one.
All of this truck
[Music]
jeans
outside.
>> Do you want to start with the
>> No, I will start with the casual. Okay.
>> With the casual.
>> Okay. Let's just start with the casual.
>> All right. Maybe tangal pink.
>> Okay.
>> But I like the pink on you.
>> The pink. Yeah, the pink would be I sent
you the picture.
>> You see what I'm saying?
>> It's not blush. It's the same thing.
>> What if it's not blush?
>> If it's not blush, I see them with the
fabric. It is nice. You like it, right?
>> But you have pink. What's this? So nice.
Okay. Okay. Can we just take it off
eong?
on a dress for the earrings.
>> So I need to buy this dress for my
earrings. Oh, mom.
>> Okay, let's go. Let's pay mom
twist and turn. That's my favorite
stair. See
my favorite.
[Music]
dinner is so beautiful
to guys.
>> Okay.
Are you sure? Oh po klay white. No but
he may baang color.
>> Are you sure to
100?
Okay. Bye. Jason, nice to see you in
person. I know kami kaya food sack mom.
Gabina na po kasi si mom shopping gabina
off the rock
sale.
Can you look? Mura na po ma 68.97
poa
4,000
ma
mura 4,000 t-shirts. Let's go. 68 68 7 *
5 35 plus tax guys
68 pesos let's dollar pala na
six
may tax my black mom my black mom
oh my god
15 minutes naang daw po 15 Ma gan na po.
Oh my god. 20 minutes.
>> Oh 9 9 824 na po ma don't like so
expensive right ano? Oh this one to how
much?
75. Oh my gosh. 7649.
[Music]
Just get a uniro.
No less
6 6500 guys
75 less
business
that's an very nice shop
guys
paper bag 6,500
ano yun le Alexander McQueen
guys I always Buy sale by season pose
parang ano shi yung parang new
>> guys it's it's night here
lot so we'll go to target we just passed
by here lot let's go
everything is so expensive in America
ma'am
[Music]
kami
one two
that's not
cell phone poy.
Oh, this is per my god. So brown lock.
Oh, you can put something purple. What
can I put in my ano? Po casing. Airpod
case. Oh, look. So cute. My lemons. I
love it. How much? Mahal naman. 14.97.
Also like this one is
cover. Oh my gosh.
lag. This one so bag also let's buy.
Oh my god. Do you like what's this p?
Mom rice taste po yan. Mom
rice p
rice p ano. What's this? I may p Oh my
umbrella phone para summer po yan mom.
Look umbrella yung phone. Mag flexible
neck. Just what's this? Look at my
umbrella phone.
Oh my gosh. No more
toys.
It's not Ras Marshall. Okay.
Mama card.
Hi. Good evening. Hi. Give me just a
second. Okay.
Mom. Okay. Na po. Very good. Okay.
What do you want to eat?
>> In and out
and out burger. Thank you poindi
parall.
Marshall s everything is closed already.
First concept
sale store. Are you finished it? Thank
you. May pancy mom
guys
$16,000
naman poanil.
Oh my god. 16 for you. 1,000.
Okay. Get more. Sure.
Make it. Okay. Try it. Try it. Okay. Oh,
she Okay, guys. Oh my gosh.
>> What do you want, Mom?
>> I want single. I don't want I just like
the normal cheeseburger and buy double
for that. Single lag, sir. Double shadow
po.
Thank you po.
>> Do I just leave you? I'll leave the car
open.
>> Yeah. Can I lock?
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. Mommy. How do I lock out?
>> Where? Okay. Lock. Unlock.
>> Lock. Okay. Go. I'll lock. In and out.
In and out. In and out.
Are there finished?
Sorry we're late.
>> It was supposed to be 2:05, but it
became 21.
>> It's supposed to be the time. Are you
okay?
>> Oh, it's supposed to be 11.
>> Okay, let's go. Hello, you little girl.
>> Hi. I'm with right now and we're going
to the outlet. Hello. Say hi, pretty
girl. lot.
You know lot
I don't want to go inside
Starbucks.
[Applause]
Let's go.
Oh my gosh.
I'm so tired.
Guys, BS Victoria Secret. Let it go.
Sakilang store. Hey Alison, did you get
a lot?
Yeah. Did you get what you wanted?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. We're waiting for you, but it's
okay. DJ, how about you?
>> Good.
>> I did not shop.
>> And yeah, good. And of course, we're
waiting for our um soup done.
I did not shop with you. What? Did you
forget something? What's that? Please
don't.
The credit card. Come. Please tell me
now what? Go back. If it's the credit
card.
>> No, it's not. What's it? my sunglasses.
>> Oh, okay. Don't use expensive
sunglasses, you know,
>> when you're like out of
>> like shopping. So, go. Let's find it.
>> I thought it's the phone, but it's not
the phone. So, it's a RL here. Okay,
we're very there over there.
>> Which is better? I think the loper
loafer or loper loafer loafer. I think
the loafer is better to you know it's
summer today. Huh?
>> Oh, you're so cute. Um, where will you
go little girl?
>> Burgers.
>> Burgers. Ah, you'll try this burger
place.
>> So, okay. Aren't you going with mom?
>> No.
>> Are you sure? So, bango. I can smell the
babango.
Sabango.
Hello, little girl. I miss you. Oh, I'm
so sad. Kiss. Kiss mama. Kiss. Kiss
mama.
So, bango gra. Did you see PJ? I show
you something. I love it. That's 40 off,
right? You said your shoes.
>> 70.
>> Oh, 70 to 50 off. Wow. Galing.
>> You can wear both.
>> So guys, enjoy.
>> Where's my sunglasses?
>> Let me there by the phone. Let me know
if the burger is good. Huh? And later
I'll see you. So, and I bring you naang
Monday. Huh?
>> We bring you Monday.
>> What time?
>> Too early. Yeah. You need good sleep on
the day before.
>> Bye.
>> Bye. Kiss mama.
>> Bye. Enjoy.
>> Okay. Phil cleaning aton's carpet. Let's
see. Kay, Phil. Okay. Show me. Show me.
You don't even know how to refill.
What's that for, baby?
Oil electricity lang. So, Phil is
cleaning this. So, aton will bring this
carpet s dorm. And thank you to Alexi.
Alex to Valon
to Aaron. Parang 3 ISM generation din
carpet nto pasa pasa lang sila they all
went to Claremont McKenna so pasa pasa
for the next batch pam ni Alison when
she lives CMC I feel okay
I'll shop now bye
mom
let's go
naman lotto shower oh my gosh let's go
Gala pala
know
pala.
>> Hey
everyone
>> thought vlogging.
>> So we're headed to what what's it
called? East something burger.
>> Easy street burger.
>> Easy street burger which is apparently
the best burger in LA. I don't believe
that but we'll see. We'll put it to the
test.
>> So, we're 10 minutes away, but I'm I'm
still doing my homework.
>> And then we're going to go shopping
after. Oh, we're going to get airwan
smoothies as well. $20 worth of
smoothies. So, we're so excited for that
to spend money again.
>> Oh, yeah. We didn't vlog yesterday.
>> No, we did not. They missed a couple
days of our lives. You want to catch
them up?
>> We had a shopping spree yesterday. So,
we're not in the mood to get ripped off
by $20 smoothies, but here
>> I feel like we just have to do it.
>> Have you ever tried it?
>> Yeah, of course. But, um, I think you
have to try it.
>> Okay. I haven't tried.
>> We'll get We'll get one each so you can
taste.
>> Okay. For the experience.
>> Stay in the right sunshine.
>> But, it's going to be I I don't know. I
don't know which one you're going to
want. If we're going to want the same
ones and
>> What do you have in mind? Like there's a
strawberry Hy the Haley Bieber one, but
I personally don't like that.
>> I want to try that cuz that's like I
guess the famous one.
>> 300 me.
>> It's not that good
>> for me. It tastes like makeup. Like
lipstick.
>> Oh no. I I hope she doesn't I hope she
doesn't like hate me after if she sees
this.
>> I love you.
>> In like maybe like 50 years or
something. You're gonna be like, "Hey,
Haley, there's like this girl from the
Philippines hating on her smoothie."
But yeah, like love I love road, but not
that smoothie. But also,
>> so you're a half Haley Bieber fan. Some
of her stuff.
>> Okay. Wow. This is a nice street. I'm
going to show. Okay. Now it's just a
trash can.
>> Great timing, Alison.
>> Picturesque drive. Is it going to be
picturesque? I think so.
>> Let's see. Well, it's cute.
Cute houses.
>> This is picturesque.
>> Is it by the hills? Yeah, it's nice.
>> He doesn't know what I'm talking about
cuz he's driving.
>> I'm taking a video of myself.
>> Okay, I'm going to end this. See you
there. Wow. Shopping.
Wow.
talaga Beverly Beverly. Wow. Favorite
place
Beverly Hills Hotel
[Music]
Guys.
But now
Rodeo Drive
segard
[Music]
my six single ba
meron Chanel.
My dog white
para hook meant
gearin
Gucci Prada
merons
IWC
ano luon
yan Louis Vuitton
yan yan po yung na Janagoodle si pretty
woman freaking woman
Robert.
Okay,
we are here now in easy streets.
So we are on easy street right now. This
is the burgers.
>> So easy
but not hard.
>> Okay, so we're going to get a reaction
from Allison. Allison, what's the
verdict?
I don't think we should be doing this in
here. Wait
>> because of the copyright reason.
>> Should I just yell? So like
>> Yeah, just yell. Just yell.
>> Where's the onion?
>> Here, taste it. It's like um
>> Oh, okay.
>> Can you see it?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. The onion looks good. I should
have gone with
>> Alison's.
>> Sorry.
>> The bun doesn't look that good.
>> Okay,
>> we'll see it.
>> See? Oo, Alissa. Big bite.
>> How is it?
>> Two bite review.
>> Good.
>> Was it worth the drive? 20 minute, 30
minute drive. So, is it the best? Nah,
not really.
>> It could be.
>> No, actually, I don't know.
>> Okay. Okay. Like burgers all taste the
same food.
>> Bye guys. We got a reaction from Alison.
>> Wow.
>> What's Wow.
>> Nothing.
>> First bite.
>> It's not the best, but it's good.
>> I agree. It's very, very good. but not
the best. So, I couldn't think of
anything better right now. But it's
pretty good.
>> So, that means it's the best.
>> Well, In-N-Out's a classic, but this
one's very tasty. Am I right? Very
tasty. And they did it in a different
way where it's smashed. You're not food
reviewer, guys.
>> Food reviewers.
>> Okay. Bye.
>> Bye, guys.
>> Say bye.
Kami smon
shop. See pretty woman walking on the
street. Pretty woman
[Music]
[Applause]
looking for a dress.
>> Mom sabi nuba. No read. Okay.
>> She she
she
ano ba? Mom
>> scaparelli.
>> Scaparelli. I cannot buy stuff. It's so
expensive for me. Just looking around.
Mom
ch
Look at the beard dress. No, there's
nothing for a sabi na tiga.
lady.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Oh, yeah. I will get something in the I
will get in the in the middle of the
back.
>> Where's your backpack?
>> I'm going to go since guys are in LA.
I'm going to eat. Let's go. Let's eat.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Alison, where are you? Mom, I'm here.
I'm just waiting for you. Mom, where are
you now?
>> Do you win?
>> They're Americans.
Mom, I'm just waiting for a 30 minutes
here. Why so girl?
[Music]
[Applause]
Mom,
>> let me go and grab her at the back.
Let me go and grab it back. Guys, I
understand what the people said of
seeing English, but I don't uh speak
very well.
[Music]
Okay, let's go.
Mom. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Let's eat Japanese.
Ginawang
[Music]
[Applause]
>> door is open for you.
>> For me?
>> Yes.
>> Very good. Because I'm hungry.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh my goodness.
>> Hi guys. So we are done eating now. And
right now Ton's doing her homework. I
like that. Responsible Allison. Let's
go.
>> It's Chad GP.
>> You use Chad GPT as a tool, right?
>> Yeah.
>> Okay, let's cut it at that. Okay, bye
guys. Our next plan is to get ice cream.
Salt and straw. We just finished Easy
Street Burger. So, ice cream time. Okay,
bye guys. Allison, where are we?
>> Van Eaton.
>> Van Eaton. Is it Van Eaton?
>> Yeah.
>> Let's show the people what's up. Like,
wow.
>> Yeah. So, it's like auction for pop
culture, right?
>> Yeah.
[Music]
from 1910.
>> Sorry.
>> Built to last. It's pretty good for 100
plus years.
>> 115.
>> That's crazy.
>> So, this is a Mudoscope. It's a
Nickelodeon. And this is how people
would watch movies back in the day
essentially. Uh, this would be in a
boardwalk or a penny arcade. And all you
got to do is put a penny in. And if you
want to bring the camera closer here,
you can actually film what's inside.
>> Oh, wow.
And it's Charlie Chaplain.
>> Yep.
>> That's pretty cool.
>> How long does it go for?
>> Oh, like a minute.
>> It's like a show.
>> Yeah.
>> And it only shows this, right?
>> Yes.
>> Yeah. I can show you the inside, too.
Here. This is one of the coolest things
I've seen.
>> You can actually see how it works here.
>> Oh, wow. So, those are all photos,
right?
>> Those are all the Those are all the
frames. Yeah. Yeah. No. And you got the
light shining. You got the thing right
here. You got this little ticker here
and it shows this is every single frame
that you just saw.
>> Uh-huh. Wow.
>> Okay. We're now here in Sunset Plaza and
we'll have Japanese food. My gosh, look
how sexy that waitress here. It's better
here. Okay, I'll stay. So, okay, we'll
order. I know now what's orderress.
>> I know now what's my orders.
>> You're so beautiful.
>> Um, we have to say is it the same? This
one is like
>> madam. I like your hair.
Pink pinkies.
And you're so sexy.
>> Thank you.
>> My favorite.
Wow, you have them.
>> Yes, I have like little um like kajuku
um pu.
>> Well, my melons.
>> Yeah, thank you.
>> Thank you.
>> I know now what's my order.
>> So, okay, we're now here. It's 5:30 in
the afternoon and I got so hungry. So,
we're now here in Sashia at sunset.
So, okay, we're waiting for an order and
I'm so hungry. Okay, I'm eating fried
rice.
>> My favorite um rock shrimp.
[Music]
Sunny LA.
We are in Salt and Straw with Allison
getting some ice cream. Ooh, smells
great. What do you plan to get? I don't
know what we'll get. We'll just show you
guys. I Ton still has homework, so got
to get moving. We are here in salt and
straw with Allison's ice cream.
>> What did you get?
>> Banana bread.
>> Banana bread with strawberry cham. All
right.
>> Sea salt with caramel ribbons.
>> Ooh, it sounds good.
>> You also have it.
>> Good. I also have it, guys. Yum. All
right. Bye, guys.
So, we are in
>> Westfield.
>> Westfield Century City in Blue Bottle
Coffee. Taste test. What did you get?
>> I don't even know.
>> It's so loud.
Is it good?
>> Yeah. I hope I don't have to go.
>> Oh, TMI.
>> PMI. TMI.
>> Guys, I'm here now at Westfield
Sanctuary and I'll meet with Alison Kasi
guys.
Alison ng um foundation and they're
asking me to watch the conjuring but
scary mom.
>> Okay. Where are you?
>> Amazon is saying oh my gosh mom you're
so l Oh my god.
>> Okay. I I asked Amazon to buy two pieces
and you buy 10 pieces.
Monica po 11 po
>> are you still inviting you're pay
>> still okay they're ask inviting me to
watch
>> are you guys watching
>> during
that said
>> we vlogged earlier mom
>> wow that's good
>> right
po naman bay
nasa yung card
they were us ready
kids don't you want to bite us am I
triple 1 x 1 xl
xl guys or no just
l
that's a small for like you
Can I drive?
>> Yes.
Oh,
you get a smaller size. What size do you
want? What size?
Okay. A yan
will be matching.
Look at
matching dy.
Okay.
[Music]
favorite scent.
Finally found
an perfume
perfume. Never mind. It's free naman
para naman mo try
ladies not
lot
so happy I I saw my favorite lot.
So we're now here in Arowan favorite
drink smoothie here and Jay Beaver
meowan
smoothie para syang road. So let's look
at let's look for guys. Everything here
is so expensive.
I think you like this smoothie, right?
chronic ill
please come.
Do you like ice cream?
[Music]
It's not so expensive here. Like it's
still a luxury item or
>> this is
>> but not so expensive pala. It's only the
smoothie. Is this the car the
restaurant? Yeah.
>> Do they have carbon here?
>> Oh, it's the restaurant. I think the one
that's um good.
>> What do you think? What did you like
from home?
>> 57.
>> Oh,
you think it's good?
>> It's 137.
>> I know. Cuz the one of three cents are
$82.
>> Yeah.
>> Wow.
>> It's 14. Huh?
>> $52,
guys. I'll just get chocolate ice cream.
So, $52. That's what guys, you know.
>> That's all one survey.
You're supposed to get the big one, but
I want to try. Try first. Try first. Try
>> these are one serving l.
>> So, okay. Let's go to right eight and
buy my favorite uh green chocolate. So,
okay, we're done with air and it's time
to go home. So, let's go to the
>> My friend is working here. And okay, PJ
wants to eat in Cheesecake Factory, but
Alison said no. We just finished our
Japanese food. We're still full. PJ, you
like cheesecake talaga?
Alison, you like to eat in cheesecake?
>> No. Cheesecake.
>> Oh, no one wants.
>> Are you coming? Cheesecake.
>> She doesn't want
>> Allison said no.
>> I know. Wait. L tita digs after what?
>> You don't want to eat? Wait. Ta digs.
>> Actually, I'm full, but I'm willing to
go with you.
>> Let's share one dish together.
>> Gosh. Dun sila na cross.
Can I cross na? Oh my gosh. Cross. Going
to Cheesecake Factory. It's red, but
they can cross. Oh, way more.
Where's my phone?
PJ. PJ.
PJ. When do I cross? Can I cross now?
Cross down. Look, you're not stopping. I
thought I have to move there. That's an
ion. Walk. Okay. Walk. Walk. Walk. Oh my
gosh. It's bow here. Ba. No. It says I
can cross mo. Mom
walking. But it's full.
My god. Cheesecake still. It's full
[Music]
cheesecake.
You remember we ate in cheesecake.
We made the bomb. You made the bomb.
yourself. Sorry.
[Music]
Hey guys, thanks for watching my vlog.
If you want to watch more videos, click
here. And if you want to watch more
videos, click here. Don't forget to
comment, like, and subscribe. Bye.
[Music]